(Penny:)Go away, Leonard.
Come on, let me
just talk to you.
(Penny:)It's open.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Penny:)I'm not going
to that party, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Okay, listen.
You don't have to wear the wig.
(Leonard:)At this party,
we're gonna win first prize
(Leonard:)just by showing up with a girl.
(Penny:)It's not the wig.
(Leonard:)Did I do something?
(Leonard:)I mean, I tried to be
friends with Zack,
(Leonard:)like you said, which believe me,
was difficult,
(Leonard:)given how you and me
used to be...
you know, "you and
me," and now you
(Leonard:)and him are
"you and him."
(Penny:)Okay, look.
We're not really "me and him."
(Leonard:)Then what are you?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Penny:)I only started seeing Zack again
(Penny:)so I wouldn't be alone
on New Year's Eve.
(Penny:)How pathetic is that?
(Leonard:)Not as pathetic
as dressing up like this
(Leonard:)and going to a comic book store
on New Year's Eve.
(Penny:)You make a cute Green Arrow.
(Leonard:)Green Lantern.